Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXIV. LOCAL LODGES
  - Sub-Series 235-2220. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2220, Northwestern Express Messengers Lodge, Portland, Oregon, 1925-1965 (Box 152, Folder 29)
      November 13, 1925-July 28, 1965. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2210, Portland, Oregon, effective July 1, 1965
  - Sub-Series 235-2223. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2223, Chicago and Western Lakes Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1956-1959 (Box 152, Folder 30)
      October 20, 1956-May 25, 1959. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2064, Chicago, Illinois, effective May 1, 1959
  - Sub-Series 235-2227. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2227, Kato Lodge, Mankato, Minnesota, 1951-1961 (Box 152, Folder 31)
      December 12, 1951-January 12, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1034, Austin, Minnesota and Lodge No. 2072, St. Paul, Minnesota, effective October 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-2229. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2229, Boise Lodge, Boise, Idaho, 1948-1962 (Box 152, Folder 32)
      September 30, 1948-April 26, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2032, Pocatello, Idaho, effective April 1, 1962
    - Lodge No. 2229, Northern Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1921-1922 (Box 152, Folder 32)
      August 30, 1921-August 14, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-2230. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2230, Pueblo Express Lodge, Pueblo, Colorado, 1930-1957 (Box 152, Folder 33)
      December 17, 1930-April 11, 1957. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2009, Denver, Colorado, effective January 1, 1957
  - Sub-Series 235-2233. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2233, Watertown, New York, 1949-1951 (Box 152, Folder 34)
      June 22, 1949-September 18, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2178, Utica, New York, effective July 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-2236. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2236, Nashville Lodge, Nashville, Tennessee, 1930 (Box 152, Folder 35)
      April 19, 1930-May 7, 1930.
  - Sub-Series 235-2237. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2237, Mountain City Lodge, DuBois, Pennsylvania, 1948-1966 (Box 152, Folder 36)
      April 11, 1948-September 28, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2144, Buffalo, New York and Lodge No. 2177, Erie, Pennsylvania, effective July 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-2242. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2242, Middlesex Lodge, Lowell, Massachusetts, 1933-1949 (Box 152, Folder 37)
      April 21, 1933-October 1, 1949. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2245, Concord, New Hampshire, effective October 1, 1949
  - Sub-Series 235-2246. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2246, Service Lodge, Williamsport, Pennsylvania, 1943-1962 (Box 152, Folder 38)
      January 5, 1943-February 1, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 616, Pottsville, Pennsylvania and Lodge No. 2001, Elmira, New York, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-2249. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2249, Washington, D.C., 1929 (Box 152, Folder 39)
      March 2, 1929-May 6, 1929. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2037, Washington, D.C., effective April 26, 1929
  - Sub-Series 235-2250. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2250, Minneapolis, Minnesota -September 28, 1929 (Box 152, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 235-2252. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2252, Rutland Lodge, Rutland, Vermont, 1947-1962 (Box 152, Folder 41)
      February 15, 1947-January 30, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2247, White River Junction, Vermont, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-2253. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2253, C.E. Meyer Lodge, Pittsfield, Massachusetts, 1929-1962 (Box 153, Folder 1)
      April 29, 1929-February 5, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2167, Springfield, Massachusetts, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-2254. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2254, Green City Lodge, Burlington, Vermont, 1946-1962 (Box 153, Folder 2)
      August 21, 1946-February 14, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2247, White River Junction, Vermont, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-2257. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2257, Buffalo, New York, 1928 (Box 153, Folder 3)
      1928 December 6
  - Sub-Series 235-2258. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2258, Boston, Massachusetts, 1930 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      1930 February 1
  - Sub-Series 235-2261. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2261, Buckeye Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1938-1939 (Box 153, Folder 5)
      January 6, 1938-January 16, 1939. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2045, Cincinnati, Ohio, effective January 1, 1939
  - Sub-Series 235-2264. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2264, Allegheny Messengers Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1931-1966 (Box 153, Folder 6)
      February 13, 1931-February 2, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2158, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, effective January 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-2265. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2265, Vancouver Lodge, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1945-1946 (Box 153, Folder 7)
      August 31, 1945-December 6, 1946. Disbanded, effective December 6, 1946
  - Sub-Series 235-2266. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2266, Fountain City Lodge, Fond du Lac, Wisconsin, 1932-1961 (Box 153, Folder 8)
      July 3, 1932-February 16, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2043, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, effective January 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-2267. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2267, Lake Shore Lodge, Sheboygan, Wisconsin, 1955-1961 (Box 153, Folder 9)
      April 25, 1955-January 20, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2043, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, effective January 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-2271. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2271, Port Jervis, New York, 1929 (Box 153, Folder 10)
      1929 July 7. Suspended, effective July 2, 1929
  - Sub-Series 235-2272. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2272, Racine Lodge, Racine, Wisconsin, 1948-1961 (Box 153, Folder 11)
      December 29, 1948-February 17, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2043, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, effective January 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-2274. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2274, Auto City Expressmens' Lodge, Pontiac, Michigan, 1930 (Box 153, Folder 12)
      1930 June 9
  - Sub-Series 235-2275. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2275, College City Lodge, Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1930-1944 (Box 153, Folder 13)
      March 23, 1930-September 13, 1944.
  - Sub-Series 235-2279. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2279, St. James Lodge, Jacksonville, Florida, 1940-1960 (Box 153, Folder 14)
      October 25, 1940-July 22, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 235-2281. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2281, United Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1961-1969 (Box 153, Folder 15)
      January 16, 1961-June 3, 1969. Formerly Lodge No. 6096, United Auxiliary Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 2040, Atlanta, Georgia, effective April 1, 1969
    - Lodge No. 2281, United Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1940-1960 (Box 153, Folder 16)
      November 20, 1940-December 29, 1960. Formerly Lodge No. 6096, United Auxiliary Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 2040, Atlanta, Georgia, effective April 1, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-2282. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2282, Expressmen Lodge, Savannah, Georgia, 1943-1964 (Box 153, Folder 17)
      September 7, 1943-October 12, 1964. Formerly Lodge No. 6117; consolidated with Lodge No. 2283, Macon, Georgia, effective October 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-2284. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2284, Railway Express Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1946-1963 (Box 153, Folder 18)
      August 28, 1946-September 17, 1963. Formerly Lodge No. 6132; consolidated with Lodges Nos. 2087 and 2219, Chicago, Illinois, effective July 1, 1963
  - Sub-Series 235-2285. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2285, Pelican Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1946-1960 (Box 153, Folder 19)
      May 2, 1946-October 24, 1960. Formerly Lodge No. 6304; consolidated with Lodge No. 1717, New Orleans, Louisiana, effective October 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-2286. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2286, Crescent Lodge, Greensboro, North Carolina, 1947-1968 (Box 153, Folder 20)
      August 18, 1947-June 24, 1968. Formerly Lodge No. 6006; consolidated with Lodge No. 2099, Greensboro, North Carolina, effective April 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-2287. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2287, Gold Hill Lodge, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1945-1968 (Box 153, Folder 21)
      March 1, 1945-August 13, 1968. Formerly Lodge No. 6013; consolidated with Lodge No. 2074, Charlotte, North Carolina, effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-2289. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2289, Florence Lodge, Florence, South Carolina, 1941-1969 (Box 153, Folder 22)
      May 29, 1941-September 10, 1969. Formerly Lodge No. 6193, Sumter Lodge, Sumter, South Carolina; consolidated with Lodge No. 2095, Florence, South Carolina, effective June 30, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-2292. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2292, Tidewater Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1946-1968 (Box 153, Folder 23)
      January 30, 1946-September 27, 1968. Formerly Lodge No. 6026; consolidated with Lodge No. 2269, Norfolk, Virginia, effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-2294. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2294, West Side Lodge, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1944-1962 (Box 153, Folder 24)
      August 26, 1944-May 2, 1962. Formerly Lodge No. 6275; consolidated with Lodge No. 1756, Greensboro, North Carolina and Lodge No. 2036, Lynchburg, Virginia, effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-2307. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2307, Centrebee Lodge, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1964-1965 (Box 153, Folder 25)
      May 12, 1964-September 24, 1965.
    - Lodge No. 2307, Centrebee Lodge, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1953-1963 (Box 153, Folder 26)
      August 14, 1953-April 1, 1963.
  - Sub-Series 235-2313. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2313, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1963-1966 (Box 153, Folder 27)
      January 29, 1963-May 4, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2302, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, effective January 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-2318. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2318, Nelson, British Columbia, Canada, 1961-1962 (Box 153, Folder 28)
      March 20, 1961-January 26, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1291, Nelson, British Columbia, Canada; Lodge No. 1292, Cranbrook, British Columbia, Canada; Lodge No. 2315, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada; and Lodge No. 2330, Lethbridge, Alberta, Canada; effective October 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-2325. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2325, Progress Lodge, New York, New York, 1947-1950 (Box 153, Folder 29)
      December 15, 1947-February 17, 1950. Suspended, effective September 23, 1949
    - Lodge No. 2325, Progress Lodge, New York, New York, 1946-1947 (Box 153, Folder 30)
      February 4, 1946-December 9, 1947. Suspended, effective September 23, 1949
    - Lodge No. 2325, Progress Lodge, New York, New York, 1930-1946 (Box 153, Folder 31)
      May 28, 1930-January 8, 1946. Suspended, effective September 23, 1949
  - Sub-Series 235-2327. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2327, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1955-1968 (Box 153, Folder 32)
      April 26, 1955-November 6, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2303, Montreal, Quebec, Canada and Lodge No. 2321, Sherbrooke, Quebec, Canada, effective October 28, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-2328. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2328, Beaver Lodge, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1954-1966 (Box 153, Folder 33)
      April 1, 1954-September 6, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2307, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada; Lodge No. 2309, Regina, Saskatchewan, Canada; Lodge No. 2310, Brandon, Manitoba, Canada; and Lodge No. 2330, Lethbridge, Alberta, Canada; effective July 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-2334. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2334, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1956 (Box 153, Folder 34)
      June 28, 1956-July 1, 1956. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2315, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, effective July 1, 1956
  - Sub-Series 235-2335. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2335, Capital Lodge, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, 1960-1962 (Box 153, Folder 35)
      July 8, 1960-October 18, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2306, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-2337. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2337, Sault Ste. Marie, Ontario, Canada, 1955-1957 (Box 153, Folder 36)
      March 8, 1955-October 9, 1957. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2319, Sudbury, Ontario, Canada, effective July 1, 1957
  - Sub-Series 235-2338. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2338, Sheaf Lodge, Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1960-1968 (Box 153, Folder 37)
      February 10, 1960-December 4, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2309, Regina, Saskatchewan, Canada; Lodge No. 2312, Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan, Canada; and Lodge No. 2316, Saskatoon, Saskatchewan, Canada; effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-2339. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2339, Foothills Lodge, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1954-1960 (Box 153, Folder 38)
      July 9, 1954-August 25, 1960. Moved to Edmonton, Alberta, Canada, effective April 19, 1956; returned to Calgary, Alberta, Canada, effective November 6, 1956; consolidated with Lodge No. 2301, Calgary, Alberta, Canada; Lodge No. 2314, Edmonton, Alberta, Canada; and Lodge No. 2332, Medicine Hat, Alberta, Canada; effective April 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-2345. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2345, Metropolitan Express Lodge, New York, New York, 1953-1962 (Box 153, Folder 39)
      August 14, 1953-December 14, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 2345, Metropolitan Express Lodge, New York, New York, 1948-1953 (Box 153, Folder 40)
      December 8, 1948-August 26, 1953.
    - Lodge No. 2345, Metropolitan Express Lodge, New York, New York, 1955 (Box 153, Folder 41)
      January 4, 1955-November 3, 1955. Subject: "Clarke and Sieffert vs. Brotherhood Corr. President Lodge 2345"
  - Sub-Series 235-2525. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 2525, Federation Lodge, New York, New York, 1928-1930 (Box 153, Folder 42)
      December 8, 1928-September 4, 1930. Suspended, effective April 1, 1930
  - Sub-Series 235-3001. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3001, Pan American Airways Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1950-1955 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      November 6, 1950-March 9, 1955. Formerly Clipper Lodge; consolidated with Lodge No. 3024, San Francisco, California, effective January 1, 1955
    - Lodge No. 3001, Magic City Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1946-1949 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      May 11, 1946-September 8, 1949.
  - Sub-Series 235-3002. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3002, Capital Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1948-1950 (Box 154, Folder 2)
      October 4, 1948-May 2, 1950. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3031, Knoxville, Tennessee, effective April 27, 1950
    - Lodge No. 3002, Panact Lodge, New York, New York, 1946-1948 (Box 154, Folder 3)
      May 17, 1946-April 1, 1948. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3003, Flushing, New York, effective April 1, 1948
  - Sub-Series 235-3003. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3003, Global Wings Lodge, Flushing, New York, 1965-1969 (Box 154, Folder 4)
      December 16, 1965-May 9, 1969. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3003, Global Wings Lodge, Flushing, New York, 1963-1965 (Box 154, Folder 5)
      January 11, 1963-December 20, 1965. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3003, Global Wings Lodge, Flushing, New York, 1961 (Box 154, Folder 6)
      February 15, 1961-November 9, 1961. Subject: "Appeal Patrick J. Leyden, Jr."; decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3003, Global Wings Lodge, Flushing, New York, 1957-1962 (Box 154, Folder 7)
      November 13, 1957-December 4, 1962. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3003, Global Wings Lodge, Flushing, New York, 1946-1957 (Box 154, Folder 8)
      May 24, 1946-November 11, 1957. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-3004. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3004, Panways Lodge, New York, New York, 1946-1949 (Box 154, Folder 9)
      May 27, 1946-February 9, 1949. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3003, Long Island City, New York, effective January 1, 1949
  - Sub-Series 235-3005. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3005, Clipper Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1964 (Box 154, Folder 10)
      February 24, 1964-May 2, 1964. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3005, Clipper Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1960-1963 (Box 154, Folder 11)
      January 8, 1960-November 15, 1963. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3005, Clipper Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1955-1959 (Box 154, Folder 12)
      March 11, 1955-December 22, 1959. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3005, Clipper Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1954 (Box 154, Folder 13)
      March 5, 1954-October 13, 1954. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3005, Clipper Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1946-1954 (Box 154, Folder 14)
      May 11, 1946-March 17, 1954. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-3006. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3006, Pan American World Airways Lodge, Houston, Texas, 1946-1969 (Box 154, Folder 15)
      June 5, 1946-July 1, 1969. Moved from Brownsville, Texas, effective February 16, 1962; decertified, effective February 19, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-3007. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3007, Panair Lodge, Seattle, Washington, 1946-1950 (Box 154, Folder 16)
      June 24, 1946-May 8, 1950. Suspended, effective April 20, 1950
  - Sub-Series 235-3008. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3008, Clipper Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1946-1969 (Box 154, Folder 17)
      June 25, 1946-May 2, 1969. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-3010. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3010, Flying Pilgrim Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1951-1953 (Box 154, Folder 18)
      January 26, 1951-November 9, 1953. Disbanded, effective August 13, 1953
    - Lodge No. 3010, Pan American Airways Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1946-1948 (Box 154, Folder 18)
      July 17, 1946-March 8, 1948. Suspended, effective November 13, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-3012. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3012, San Juan Lodge, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1951-1962 (Box 154, Folder 19)
      June 18, 1951-October 12, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 3012, San Juan Lodge, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1962-1969 (Box 154, Folder 19a)
      November 9, 1962-May 8, 1969. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3012, Sky Line Lodge, Mobile, Alabama, 1948-1951 (Box 154, Folder 20)
      October 4, 1948-June 21, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3031, Knoxville, Tennessee, effective July 1, 1951
    - Lodge No. 3012, Northwest Airlines Lodge, Newark, New Jersey, 1946-1947 (Box 154, Folder 21)
      July 24, 1946-November 12, 1947. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3017, New York, New York, effective November 12, 1947
  - Sub-Series 235-3014. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3014, Airline Porters Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1951-1962 (Box 154, Folder 22)
      August 30, 1951-March 14, 1962. Disbanded, effective December 31, 1961
    - Lodge No. 3014, Tropical Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1946-1948 (Box 154, Folder 22)
      July 26, 1946-July 4, 1948. Suspended, effective May 19, 1948
  - Sub-Series 235-3016. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3016, Top Flight Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1946-1948 (Box 154, Folder 23)
      August 1, 1946-April 6, 1948. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3015, Minneapolis, Minnesota, effective March 31, 1948
  - Sub-Series 235-3020. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3020, Northwest Airlines Lodge, Fargo, North Dakota, 1946-1958 (Box 154, Folder 24)
      August 22, 1946-December 11, 1958. Moved from Bismarck, North Dakota, 1947; consolidated with Lodge No. 3015, Minneapolis, Minnesota, effective October 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-3021. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3021, Air Express Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1946-1949 (Box 154, Folder 25)
      November 29, 1946-May 24, 1949.
  - Sub-Series 235-3022. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3022, Explorer Lodge, Eau Gallie, Florida, 1966-1969 (Box 154, Folder 26)
      May 17, 1966-August 25, 1969. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3022, Explorer Lodge, Eau Gallie, Florida, 1963-1965 (Box 154, Folder 27)
      August 19, 1963-December 28, 1965. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3022, Explorer Lodge, Eau Gallie, Florida, 1958-1962 (Box 155, Folder 1)
      February 10, 1958-June 6, 1962. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3022, Tropical Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1952-1957 (Box 155, Folder 2)
      July 3, 1952-December 23, 1957. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3050, New York, New York, effective April 1, 1957
    - Lodge No. 3022, Chicago, Illinois, 1947-1948 (Box 155, Folder 2)
      May 3, 1947-March 20, 1948.
  - Sub-Series 235-3023. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3023, Capitol Airlines Lodge, Washington, D.C., 1947-1961 (Box 155, Folder 3)
      May 28, 1947-December 31, 1961. Disbanded, effective December 31, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-3024. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3024, Strato Lodge, South San Francisco, California, 1952-1969 (Box 155, Folder 4)
      July 8, 1952-June 6, 1969. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3024, Pan Victory Lodge, New York, New York, 1947-1949 (Box 155, Folder 5)
      June 3, 1947-March 18, 1949. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3003, Long Island City, New York, effective January 1, 1949
  - Sub-Series 235-3025. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3025, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1967-1961 (Box 155, Folder 6)
      June 4, 1967-July 18, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3026, Chicago, Illinois, effective July 1, 1961
    - Lodge No. 3025, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1964-1969 (Box 155, Folder 7)
      March 19, 1964-August 25, 1969. Decertified, effective March 27, 1969
  - Sub-Series 235-3026. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3026, Capitalaire Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1947-1962 (Box 155, Folder 8)
      June 9, 1947-January 25, 1962. Disbanded, effective December 31, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-3027. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3027, Capital Fleet Lodge, New York, New York, 1947-1962 (Box 155, Folder 9)
      June 6, 1947-January 19, 1962. Disbanded, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-3028. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3028, Constitution Lodge, Washington, D.C., 1947-1961 (Box 155, Folder 10)
      June 10, 1947-December 31, 1961. Disbanded, effective December 31, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-3029. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3029, Panair Lodge, Seattle, Washington, 1952-1969 (Box 155, Folder 11)
      July 8, 1952-May 8, 1969. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3029, Heart of America Lodge, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1947-1950 (Box 155, Folder 12)
      June 11, 1947-February 15, 1950. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3038, Kansas City, Missouri, effective January 1, 1950
  - Sub-Series 235-3030. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3030, Upstate Lodge, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1947-1961 (Box 155, Folder 13)
      June 11, 1947-December 31, 1961. Disbanded, effective December 31, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-3031. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3031, Skyway Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1947-1963 (Box 155, Folder 14)
      June 11, 1947-May 2, 1963. Moved from Knoxville, Tennessee, effective May 27, 1959; disbanded, effective December 31, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-3032. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3032, Buckeye Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1947-1962 (Box 155, Folder 15)
      June 12, 1947-October 1, 1962. Disbanded, effective December 31, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-3033. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3033, Clipper Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1952-1969 (Box 155, Folder 16)
      September 19, 1952-May 2, 1969. Decertified, effective February 19, 1969
    - Lodge No. 3033, NEA Skymaster Lodge, New York, New York, 1947-1951 (Box 155, Folder 17)
      June 14, 1947-March 16, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 3010, Boston, Massachusetts, effective January 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-3034. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3034, Capital Airlines Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1947-1962 (Box 155, Folder 18)
      June 16, 1947-September 25, 1962. Disbanded, effective December 31, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-3035. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 3035, Capital Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1947-1962 (Box 155, Folder 19)
      June 19, 1947-January 26, 1962. Disbanded, effective December 31, 1961